1. println("I am inside beforeTest")
1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://www.usertesting.com/get-paid-to-test")
9. rightClick(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Get Paid to Test  Make Money Online  S_84d4cb/img_Get started_lazyloaded"))
13. rightClick(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Get Paid to Test  Make Money Online  S_84d4cb/h1_Boost your monthly income in your free time"))
17. rightClick(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Get Paid to Test  Make Money Online  S_84d4cb/p_Try the ultimate side hustle. Its easy, f_9b9a41"))
21. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Get Paid to Test  Make Money Online  S_84d4cb/h1_Boost your monthly income in your free time"), "Boost your monthly income in your free time")
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_(2) New Messages/p_Try the ultimate side hustle. Its easy, f_9b9a41"), "Try the ultimate side hustle. It’s easy, fast, and simple. Share your perspective on products and experiences and make money online from the comfort of your home.")
29. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Get Paid to Test  Make Money Online  S_84d4cb/button_Get started"), 0)
33. rightClick(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_(2) New Messages/img_Learn more_ls-is-cached lazyloaded"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_(2) New Messages/div_Learn more_vertical-tab-right-content-2"))
41. verifyElementClickable(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Get Paid to Test  Make Money Online  S_84d4cb/a_Sign In"))
45. closeBrowser()
1. println("I am inside afterTest")